Guide to the Betsy Wade Papers WAG.020
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Betsy Wade Papers
1966-1993
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Wade, Betsy
WAG.020
16.25 linear feet in 16 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
Betsy Wade was a journalist who worked for many years for the New York Times, a member of the Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, and a founding member of New York Trade Union Women and of the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW). The Betsy Wade Papers (dated 1966-1993) consists of materials created and collected by Wade documenting her career in journalism, her engagement with the Newspaper Guild of New York, and her involvement with labor organizing more broadly, with particular emphasis on gender discrimination. The collection also documents the activities and internal divisions within the Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Biographical Note
Betsy Wade (1929-2020) was a journalist and active member of the Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, as well as a founding member of New York Trade Union Women and of the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW). Throughout her career, Wade was an active union organizer, serving as a shop steward, picket captain, and officer in the Newspaper Guild.
Wade joined The New York Times as a copy editor in 1956, making her the first woman to edit news for the publication. She was the first woman editor on the foreign copy desk, as well as the first woman deputy chief of the foreign copy desk, a position which she held during the Vietnam War.
In the fall of 1972, the Women's Studies Institute of Cornell University, in collaboration with the Region II Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, held a meeting of labor union staff meetings to discuss issues concerning the role of women in unions. This group, which became known as New York Trade Union Women, began to meet monthly for "brown bag" lunches, and called the first New York Trade Union Women's Conference in January 1974.
CLUW was founded in March 1974 in Chicago, adopting four basic goals of action: to promote affirmative action in the workplace; to strengthen the role of women in unions; to organize unorganized women workers; and to increase the involvement of women in the political and legislative process. In 1974, Wade was one of seven plaintiffs in a successful class action suit against the New York Times for gender discrimination. In 1975, New York Trade Union Women became the New York City chapter of CLUW.
Wade was an active member of the Newspaper Guild of New York, and was nominated by petition both times she ran for the presidency of Local 3 (as-opposed to the union's more usual procedure in which a candidate is nominated by the local's Representative Assembly by a quorum of member representing a certain number of shops). Her election to her second term (which began in 1980) was challenged by the losing candidates, who forced a re-run of the election (supervised by the Department of Labor) in September 1982. Wade did not run for president in this election re-run; instead she ran for membership on the Local's Executive Committee. She and all the members of her insurgent Membership Slate were defeated in this election. In December 1982 Wade also ran unsuccessfully for the office of Local Executive Vice President. Wade also served three times as a regional president of the Guild's International. She ran unopposed for her first term (as was usual in elections for this position), but the elections for her next two terms were contested.
Sources:
Coalition of Labor Women. "About CLUW." 11 August 2008. http://www.cluw.org/about.html
Roth, Silke. Building Movement Bridges: The Coalition of Labor Union Women. Westport, CT: Praeger, 2003.
Columbia Journalism Alumni Journal, Winter 2002.
Scope and Contents
The Betsy Wade Papers (dated 1966-1993) consists of materials created and collected by Wade documenting her career in journalism, her engagement with the Newspaper Guild of New York, and her involvement with labor organizing more broadly, with particular emphasis on gender discrimination. The collection also documents the activities and internal divisions within the Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3. Materials in this collection include photographs of demonstrations and other events; correspondence between Wade and other members of the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW); administrative documents from the New York City CLUW chapter; subject files on occupational sexism and women's rights more broadly; and correspondence, meeting minutes, handwritten notes, and ephemera concerning Wade's involvement in the Newspaper Guild of New York.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into four series:
Series I. Coalition of Labor Women, 1972-1982
Series II. Photographs, 1978-1982
Series III. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1966-1984
Series IV. New York Walking Tours, 1979-1993
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Betsy Wade in 1982. The accession number associated with this gift is 1982.001. Wade donated an accretion of materials concerning the Newspaper Guild of New York in 1986; the accession number associated with this gift is 1995.004. Photographic materials were donated at a date that was not recorded; the accession numbers associated this collection are 1950.155 and 1995.004. In 2020, Wade donated an accretion of materials concerning labor history walking tours; the accession number associated with this gift is 2021.018.
Fliers (printed matter); Newsletters.; New York (N.Y.).; Clippings (information artifacts); Brochures.; Correspondence.; Women labor union members -- New York (N.Y.); Women in the labor movement -- United States; Women labor union members -- Societies, etc.; Strikes and lockouts -- Newspapers -- New York (N.Y.); Journalists -- Labor unions.; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.). New York City Chapter; New York Trade Union Women; Krupsak, Mary Anne; Stern, Marjorie; Strandt, Pat; Abzug, Bella S., 1920-1998; Wade, Betsy; Newspaper Guild of New York; New York Times Company
- Series I. Coalition of Labor Women, 1972-1982; 1 linear foot in 2 manuscript boxes
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of correspondence between Wade and other leaders of the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), including Marjorie Stern, Pat Strandt and Luella Hansberry, as well as material relating to CLUW conferences and conventions. Administrative materials relating to the New York City Chapter of CLUW, including by-laws, election materials, newsletters, reports, resolutions and statements are also present. Also included are clippings and subject files documenting CLUW's efforts on behalf of working women, including material on the Equal Rights Amendment (1980), the Senatorial campaign of Bella Abzug (1976) and Mary Anne Krupsak's campaign for Lieutenant Governor of New York (1974).
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Annual Awards Dinner-Dance, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CLUW-IN (newsletter), 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CLUW News (newsletter), 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Conferences: Coalition of Labor Union Women Regional Conference (New York, NY), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Conferences: First New York Trade Union Women's Conference (New York, NY), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Conferences: "Pay Equity: Issue for the 80's" (New York, NY), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Convention (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Convention (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Convention (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Convention (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Convention (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: New York City Chapter, Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: New York City Chapter, Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: New York Trade Union Women's Conference, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Elections (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Equal Rights Amendment: March on Richmond, VA, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Legislation, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Membership Lists and Biographies, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Membership Meetings, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - National Coordinating Committee (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Publicity Materials (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Reports, Resolutions and Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Senator Krupsak for Lieutenant Governor Committee, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Steering Committee (Coalition of Labor Union Women), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Union Women for Bella Abzug, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Series II. Photographs, 1978-1982; .5 linear feet in 1 manuscript box
  This series consists of 28 photographs (all but two are black and white), ranging from 2x3 to 8x10 prints, 24 photograph negatives, and two leaflets. The photographs include portraits of Betsy Wade and fellow-members of dissident factions that ran for offices in The Newspaper Guild, Local 3, picket lines and demonstrations (including some for the 1981 strike against the New York Timesand participation by a delegation of Newspaper Guild members in the 1982 "No Nukes" New York City demonstration), and of a press conference with newspaper corporate executive Rupert Murdoch, labor arbitrator Theodore Kheel, and George McDonald (president of the Allied Printing Trades Council). Other individuals identified include (but are not limited to): Joy Cook, Frank Emblen, Eli Holtzman, Frank Mazza, and Betsy Wade. Some of the photographs were shot by Ruby Washington. The leaflets are election campaign publications for two dissident slates within The Newspaper Guild, Local 3--the "Responsibility Slate," 1978; and "The Membership Slate," 1980--both feature photographs and biographies of the candidates.
  Folders are arranged topically.
  - Portraits: Local 3 Newspaper Guild Election Campaign, 12/78, nd., 10/80—(incl.) Betsy Wade, Joy Cook, Frank Emblen, Eli Holtzman, Frank Mazza, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Strikes, Demonstrations, and Parades: 5/81 strike against the New York Times; 6/12/82 anti-nuclear demonstration at United Nations; 9/7/81 Labor Day Parade—Fifth Avenue—Times Unit [of the Newspaper Guild—Local 3]; c. 1982, Local 3 participation in Washington [DC] march, possibly Equal Rights Amendment support, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified: 5/28/80—Local 3 delegates before International Executive Board, Washington, DC; 4/7/81, McDonald, Kheel w/ Murdoch speaking at press conference., 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Negatives: Rank and file delegates from Local 3 appear before IEB April 28, 1980 to describe impact of continued high dues on their fellow members and on their work as steward; More of rank and file delegates before IEB, Washington, D.C. 4/28/80; Times Unit officers at Publishers Association of NY, 1 Penn Plaza just before opening negotiations at 6:20 PM, 2/18/81., 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Series III. Newpaper Guild of New York, 1966-1984; 7.75 linear feet in 15 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  This series consists of Betsy Wade's personal collection of records of and relating to the Newspaper Guild and its Local 3, primarily dated 1975 to 1984, as well as materials given to Wade by Rose Mary Mechem that relate to the Guild's policies regarding involvement in (United States) government-supported or government-sponsored organizations and programs in Latin American and elsewhere abroad.
  The focus of most of these documents is on the activities of Wade and an "insurgent caucus" with which she was associated in the International and in Local 3. These materials document a lively struggle between the insurgents and their supporters (variously called the Reponsibility Slate, the Membership Slate, etc.) and the insurgents' opponents (different individuals and slates variously called the Democratic Coalition, the Representative Assembly Slate, the Unity Slate, etc.) at every level of the organization and on practically every issue.
  Throughout the series, which covers a fairly broad spectrum of Guild concerns and activities, and in which are represented all levels of the organization, this conflict is evident particularly in the group of materials concerned with elections and referenda. Here are gathered materials on more than twenty-five elections, referenda, and public disputes that took place in Local 3 in the years from 1978 to 1984. These materials (the bulk of which are campaign literature) demonstrate a chronological picture of the issues and personalities at the core of the conflicts within the Guild.
  Another group of materials in series concentrates on one particular aspect of these conflicts: disagreements at the Guild-wide level over Guild involvement in government-supported or government-sponsored programs in foreign countries. These materials document the struggle, within the Guild over this issue, which began as early as 1967, with revelations of CIA involvement in the American Institute for Free Labor Development (AIFLD) that resulted in the termination of TNG-AIFLD joint programs, and re-emerged in the late 1970s and early 1980s with the resumption of these programs. Much of this material is drawn from documents gathered by Rose Mary Mechem and given to Betsy Wade, although a significant amount also comes from Wade, who also collected materials on the subject.
  While the majority of this series focuses on the internal struggle in the Guild, it is also documents a broader range of concerns regarding the administration and activities of a labor union. The minutes of the International Executive Board of TNG, of the Executive Committee of Local 3, and the Representative Assembly and General Membership Meeting of Local 3 are particularly useful in this regard (although there are some gaps in this documentation).
  Interfiled throughout the series are handwritten notes, some of which are marginal notations written directly onto various documents (such as meeting agendas) that record, for example, whether Wade attended a particular meeting or when and how many copies of a leaflet were distributed. Others, however, are far more extensive: personal minutes, for example, of meetings, and notes on telephone conversations, with some dialog recorded verbatim. On occasion these notes are separate individual documents, but more often they are written on the front or back of preexisting documents such as leaflets. Most of these notes appear to be in Wade's hand. A sample of Wade's handwriting is included in the appendices, to assist the researcher in making this determination.
  The series is arranged in alphabetically.
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development (AIFLD) -- Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Developement (AIFLD) -- Newspaper Clippings and Leaflets on AIFLD-CIA Connection, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development (AIFLD) -- Convention Packet, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development (AIFLD) -- Correspondence, 1967-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development (AIFLD) -- Correspondence, 1967-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development (AIFLD) -- NGNY Sub-Grant, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Amsterdam News Unit, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bacheller, Don -- Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Conference of Councils -- By-Laws, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CURE (Consolidated Unions Research Effort Trust) -- Correspondence, Contracts, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Consumers Union Unit, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Contracts (By Unit A-Z), 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Daily News Unit -- Bargaining, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Daily News Unit -- Elections and Referendums, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Daily News Unit -- Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC) Cases, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Daily News Unit -- Guild Strike News, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Daily News Unit -- Sale, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Daily News Unit -- Strike, 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Daily News Unit -- Unit Clarification Notes, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Daily World Unit, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Donner, Suzanne (NGNY Secretary-Treasurer) -- Resignation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Frontpage -- Education and Publicity Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Frontpage -- Letters to the Editor, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Frontpage -- President's Column, Various Drafts, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Frontpage -- Story Drafts, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Great Lakes District Council, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Home News Unit (New Brunswick, NJ) -- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - International Association of Publisher's Employees (IAPE), 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Local 3 -- Ad Hoc Committees, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Local 3 -- Administrative Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Local 3 -- Bulletin, 1986-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
  - Local 3 -- Bulletin Story Drafts, 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Local 3 -- Committees, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Local 3 -- Contract Enforcement Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local 3 -- Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box 4, Folder 14-16)
  - Local 3 -- Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Local 3 -- Elections, 1976-1995 (Box 5, Folder 4-9)
  - Local 3 -- Elections and Referendums Rules, 1976-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Local 3 -- Elections Committee, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Local 3 -- Elections Committee -- Radio Free Europe Dispute, 1967-1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Local 3 -- Elections Re-run of 1980 Election, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Local 3 -- Elections -- Tally Sheets and Ballots, 1967-1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Local 3 -- Executive Committee Agendas, Minutes, and Motions, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Local 3 -- Executive Committee Agendas, Minutes, and Motions, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
  - Local 3 -- Executive Committee Correspondence and Reports, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Local 3 -- Executive Committee Rules (Drafts), 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Local 3 -- Finance Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Local 3 -- General Membership Meeting, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local 3 -- General Membership Meeting Announcements, Agendas, Minutes, 1978-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Local 3 -- General Membership Meeting President's Reports/Speeches To, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Local 3 -- Headquarters Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Local 3 -- Human Rights Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Local 3 -- Legal Bills, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Local 3 -- Membership and Shop Stewards Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 3 -- Officers, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Local 3 -- Organizing Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Local 3 -- Organizing (New Haven), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Local 3 -- Organizing (New York), 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Local 3 -- Open Shop/Magazine Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Local 3 -- Petitions and Petition Forms, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Local 3 -- Referendums, December 1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Local 3 -- Representative Assembly, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - Local 3 -- Representative Assembly Meeting, June 18, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Local 3 -- Representative Assembly Minutes, Agendas, Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - Local 3 -- Resignation Cases, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Local 3 -- Staff Contracts, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Local 3 -- Staff Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Local 3 -- Strike Benefits Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Local 3 -- Trial Board, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Local 10 -- Philadelphia Evening Bulletin NLRB Decision, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Local 10 -- Philadelphia Evening Bulletin Organizing, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Local 35 (Washington D.C. - Baltimore) Organizing Leaflets, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Middle Atlantic District Council, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Middle Atlantic District Council Minutes, 1975-1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Midwest District Council Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - National Society of Operative Printers, Graphical and Media Personnel (England), 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - National Union of Journalists (England), 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - New England District Council, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - New York Post -- Bargaining, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - New York Times -- Arbitrations, 1979-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - New York Times -- Bargaining, 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12-14)
  - New York Times -- Bargaining, 1976-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Times -- Benefits, 1981-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - New York Times -- Clippings, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New York Times -- Correspondence, 1983-1994 (Box 11, Folder 5-7)
  - New York Times -- Financial Reports, 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - New York Times -- Job Descriptions, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - New York Times -- Referendums, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - New York Times -- Rosario Case (Minorities Class Action Suit Against New York Times), 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - New York Times -- Union Times, 1983-1995 (Box 12, Folder 3-6)
  - New York Times -- Union Times -- Story Drafts, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - New York Times -- Unit Clarification, 1979-1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - New York Times -- Unit Clarification -- Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Administrative Manual, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Arbitrations, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Audits, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 2-5)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Collective Bargaining Manuals, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Concerned Guild Members, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Contract Index, November 1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Convention, 1967-1980 (Box 13, Folder 9-11)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Convention -- Election -- Democratic Coalition Slate Leaflets, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Convention -- Election Leaflets, May 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Convention -- Elections -- Membership Slate, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Convention -- Women's Meeting, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- Guild Reporter Advertising Policies, 1966-1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Election and Referendum Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York (NGNY) -- International Executive Board (IEB) -- Appeals Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)